Lewis W. Douglas papers, 1859-1974 (bulk 1880-1960)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IV: Lewis W. Douglas Papers, 1906-1974
  - Subseries II: State Legislature and Congress, 1923-1933
    - 72nd Congress, Legislation, 1931-1933
      - Tariff, Copper (Petition to President Hoover). April 1932 (Box 203, Folder 5)
      - Tariff, Copper (Resolutions by various groups). no date (Box 203, Folder 6-8)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, Walter Douglas and J.S. Douglas). no date (Box 204, Folder 1)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, W.F. Ferris, United Verde Copper Co.). no date (Box 204, Folder 2)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, Carl Hayden). no date (Box 204, Folder 3)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, Governor G.W.P. Hunt). no date (Box 204, Folder 4)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, W.W. Lynch). no date (Box 204, Folder 5)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, F.W. Maclennan, Miami Copper Co.). no date (Box 204, Folder 6)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, Sam Morris). no date (Box 204, Folder 7)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, Phelps Dodge Corporation). no date (Box 204, Folder 8)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, John R. Towles). no date (Box 204, Folder 9)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, Cleve Van Dyke, Arizona Copper Tariff Comm.). no date (Box 204, Folder 10)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, E.H. Westlake, Miami Copper Co.). no date (Box 204, Folder 11)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, U.S. Tariff Commission). no date (Box 204, Folder 12)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, LWD and office). no date (Box 205, Folder 1)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, various A-J). no date (Box 205, Folder 2)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, various K-Z). no date (Box 205, Folder 3)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, general). no date (Box 205, Folder 4-8)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, sent by C.F. Willis, ed. The Mining Journal). no date (Box 205, Folder 9)
      - Tariff, Copper (correspondence, sent by A. White, Levy Brothers, Arizona). no date (Box 205, Folder 10)
      - Tariff, Copper (U.S. Tariff Commission: Report on Copper Investigation). November 30, 1931 (Box 206, Folder 1-2)
      - Tariff, Copper (LWD's form letter). January 30, 1932 (Box 206, Folder 3)
      - Tariff, Copper (LWD's form letter). March 9, 1932 (Box 206, Folder 4-5)
      - Tariff, Copper (U.S. Senate, Committee on Finance: An Import Tax on Copper). April 1932 (Box 206, Folder 6)
      - Tariff, Copper (Hoval A. smith: publications and speeches). no date (Box 206, Folder 7)
      - Tariff, Copper (clippings). no date (Box 207, Folder 1-4)
      - Tariff, Copper (Arizona Taxes, Bonds, Expenditures). no date (Box 207, Folder 5)
      - Tariff, Copper (Arizona mining unemployment statistics). no date (Box 207, Folder 6)
      - Tariff, Copper (statistical material). no date (Box 207, Folder 7)
      - Tariff, Copper (foreign wage scales). no date (Box 207, Folder 8)
      - Tariff, Copper (articles, reprints, speeches, etc). no date (Box 207, Folder 9)
      - Tariff, Copper (miscellaneous material). no date (Box 207, Folder 10)
      - Summarized Data of Copper Production, U.S. Department of Commerce, Bureau of Mines, Economic paper 1. 1928 (Box 207)
      - Summarized Data of Lead Production, U.S. Department of Commerce, Bureau of Mines, Economic paper 5). 1929 (Box 207)
      - Arizona Silver Belt (national edition). October and November 1931 (Box 207)
      - Copper (publication in Miami, Arizona). December 1931 and January 1932 (Box 207)
      - Tariff, Silver & Gold (bills). no date (Box 208, Folder 1)
      - Tariff, Silver & Gold (correspondence). no date (Box 208, Folder 2-3)
      - Tariff, Silver & Gold (hearings). no date (Box 208, Folder 4)
      - Tariff, Silver & Gold (clippings). no date (Box 208, Folder 5)
      - Tariff, Silver & Gold (speeches). no date (Box 208, Folder 6)
      - Tariff, Silver & Gold (miscellaneous publications). no date (Box 208, Folder 7)
      - Tax legislation, "revenue bill" (correspondence). no date (Box 209, Folder 1-2)
      - Tax legislation, "revenue bill" (clippings, miscellaneous material). no date (Box 209, Folder 3)
      - War Debt Moratorium (bills, notes, etc). no date (Box 209, Folder 4)
      - War Debt Moratorium (correspondence). no date (Box 209, Folder 5)
      - War Debt Moratorium (miscellaneous publications). no date (Box 209, Folder 6)
      - War Debt Moratorium (clippings). no date (Box 209, Folder 7)
      - Waterways. no date (Box 209, Folder 8)
      - Veterans, "bonus bill" (bills, speeches, etc). no date (Box 210, Folder 1)
      - Veterans, "bonus bill" (general correspondence). no date (Box 210, Folder 2)
      - Veterans, "bonus bill" (correspondence with F.L.J. Carroll and LWD's "bonus letter"). no date (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - Veterans, "bonus bill" (form letters received). no date (Box 210, Folder 4)
      - Veterans, "bonus bill" (letters received). no date (Box 210, Folder 5)
      - Veterans, "bonus bill" (clippings). no date (Box 210, Folder 6)
      - Veterans, Emergency Officers' Retirement (bills, correspondence). no date (Box 210, Folder 7)
      - Veterans, "bonus bill" (Emergency Officers' Retirement (correspondence with J.A. McGuire). no date (Box 210, Folder 8)
      - Veterans (war risk insurance). no date (Box 211, Folder 1)
      - Veterans (Pensions for Widows, Children, Dependent Parents, H.R.7534 and H.R. 8578). no date (Box 211, Folder 2)
      - Veterans (Pensions for Widows, Children, Dependent Parents, H.R. 7230). no date (Box 211, Folder 3)
      - Veterans (miscellaneous veterans legislation). no date (Box 211, Folder 4)
      - Veterans (miscellaneous printed material). no date (Box 211, Folder 5)
      - Veterans' Affairs: Hearings before the Joint Congressional Committee on Veterans' Affairs, 72nd Congress, 2nd Session, 3 volumes. December 9, 1932-January 30, 1933 (Box 211)
      - Laws relating to U.S. Veterans' Bureau and War Risk Insurance, compiled by Elmer A. Lewis, Supt. Document Room, House of Representatives. 1930, 1931, 1932 (Box 211)
      - Banking (bills, correspondence). no date (Box 212, Folder 1)
      - Banking (material on short selling). no date (Box 212, Folder 2)
      - Banking (miscellaneous material, clippings). no date (Box 212, Folder 3)
      - Communism. no date (Box 212, Folder 4)
      - District of Columbia. no date (Box 212, Folder 5)
      - Flood Control at Nogales, Arizona-Mexico. no date (Box 212, Folder 6)
      - Interstate Commerce Act (amendments to "recapture clause"). no date (Box 212, Folder 7)
      - Letters Patent (renewals, extensions, etc). no date (Box 212, Folder 8)
      - Motor Transportation. no date (Box 212, Folder 9)
      - Pensions. no date (Box 212, Folder 10)
      - Philippine Independence. no date (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - Resale (Capper-Kelly Fair Trade Bill). no date (Box 213, Folder 2)
      - Work Week. no date (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - Zinsser and Company, relief of. no date (Box 213, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous, A-B. no date (Box 213, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous, C-H. no date (Box 213, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous, I-O. no date (Box 213, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous, P-Z. no date (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - 72nd Congress, Economy File, 1931-1933
      - Economy Committee (correspondence). no date (Box 214, Folder 1)
      - Economy Committee (correspondence: Editor of Haverhill Gazette, Mass.) no date (Box 214, Folder 2)
      - Economy Committee (Bill "To Effect Economies in the National Government," H.R. 11597). no date (Box 214, Folder 3)
      - Economy Committee (clippings). no date (Box 214, Folder 4)
      - Economy Committee (miscellaneous). no date (Box 214, Folder 5)
      - Economy bill, H.R. 11267 no date (Box 214, Folder 6)
      - Speeches on balancing the budget, Douglas & Crisp. 1932 (Box 214, Folder 7)
      - National Economy League. no date (Box 214, Folder 8)
      - President of the U.S. (various messages to Congress). no date (Box 214, Folder 9)
      - Department of Agriculure (bills, notes, etc). no date (Box 215, Folder 1)
      - Department of Agriculture (correspondence). no date (Box 215, Folder 2)
      - Department of Commerce. no date (Box 215, Folder 3)
      - Department of Commerce. no date (Box 215, Folder 4)
      - Department of the Navy (correspondence, notes). no date (Box 215, Folder 5)
      - Department of the Navy (miscellaneous material). no date (Box 215, Folder 6)
      - Federal Farm Board. no date (Box 215, Folder 7)
      - Post Office Department. no date (Box 215, Folder 8)
      - U.S. Civil Service Commission. no date (Box 215, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous Departments, Commissions, etc. no date (Box 216, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous Departmetns, Commissions, etc. no date (Box 216, Folder 2)
      - Federal Board for Vocational Education. no date (Box 216, Folder 3)
      - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America. no date (Box 216, Folder 4)
      - Economy (speeches and articles). no date (Box 216, Folder 5)
      - Economy (clippings). no date (Box 216, Folder 6)
      - Foreign Economy (miscellaneous material). no date (Box 216, Folder 7)
      - Veterans Administration. no date (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - Veterans Administration (clippings). no date (Box 217, Folder 2)
      - Veterans Administration (LWD's speech in Congress on the "Economy Bill"). May 3, 1932 (Box 217, Folder 3)
      - Veterans Administration (Veterans Title, IX, "Economy Bill," correspondence). no date (Box 217, Folder 4-5)
      - Veterans Administration (Veterans Title, IX, "Economy Bill," form letter to correspondence). no date (Box 217, Folder 6)
      - Veterans Administration, LWD's radio speech on Veterans (draft, clippings). no date (Box 217, Folder 7)
      - Veterans Administration, LWD's radio speech on Veterans (correspondence, Arizona). no date (Box 217, Folder 8)
      - Veterans Administration, LWD's radio speech on Veterans (correspondence, not Arizona). no date (Box 217, Folder 9)
      - War Department (notes, miscellaneous material). no date (Box 218, Folder 1)
      - War Department (material on personnel). no date (Box 218, Folder 2-3)
      - War Department (material on schools, ROTC, training camps, etc). no date (Box 218, Folder 4)
      - War Department (Appropriations Bill). no date (Box 218, Folder 5)
      - War Department (correspondence regarding Appropriations Bill). no date (Box 218, Folder 6-7)
      - Annual Report of the Secretary of War. 1931 (Box 218)
      - The National Defense Act, approved June 3, 1916, The Pay Readjustment Act, approved June 10, 1922, Army and Navy Pay Tables, March 1929, printed for Committee on Military Affairs, House of Representatives, 70th Congress. no date (Box 218)
      - Salary Reductions for Federal Employees (correspondence). no date (Box 219, Folder 1-4)
      - Salary Reductions for Federal Employees (correspondence answered by LWD's mimeographed letter). no date (Box 219, Folder 5-6)
      - Salary Reductions for Federal Employees (clippings). no date (Box 219, Folder 7)
      - Charts prepared for the Economy Committee, Department of Agriculture. no date (Box 220, Folder 1)
      - Charts prepared for the Economy Committee, Department of the Interior. no date (Box 220, Folder 2)
      - Charts prepared for the Economy Committee, Department of Commerce. no date (Box 220, Folder 3)
      - Charts prepared for the Economy Committee, General Accounting Office. no date (Box 220, Folder 4)
      - Charts prepared for the Economy Committee, Functional Classifications of 1933, Estimates and 1932 Appropriations. no date (Box 220, Folder 5)
      - Charts prepared for the Economy Committee, Department of Labor. no date (Box 221, Folder 1)
      - Charts prepared for the Economy Committee, Interstate Commerce Commission. no date (Box 221, Folder 2)
      - Charts prepared for the Economy Committee, Post Office. no date (Box 221, Folder 3)
      - Charts prepared for the Economy Committee, War Department. no date (Box 221, Folder 4)
      - Charts prepared for the Economy Committee, Department of Justice. no date (Box 222, Folder 1)
      - Charts prepared for the Economy Committee, Department of State. no date (Box 222, Folder 2)
      - Charts prepared for the Economy Committee, Independent Establishments. no date (Box 222, Folder 3)
      - Charts prepared for the Economy Committee, Department of the Treasury. no date (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - 70-72nd Congresses, Veterans Compenation Claims, 1927-1933
      - Veterans Compensation Claims, A-E. no date (Box 223)
      - Veterans Compensation Claims, F-J. no date (Box 224)
      - Veterans Compensation Claims, K-Maw. no date (Box 225)
      - Veterans Compensation Claims, Max-R. no date (Box 226)
      - Veterans Compensation Claims, S-Z. no date (Box 227)
    - U.S. Service Academies
      - Lists of Candidates. no date (Box 228, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous. no date (Box 228, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, Navy Department, Bureau of Navigation, War Department, Adjutant General. no date (Box 228, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, U.S. Civil Service Commission. no date (Box 228, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, Out of State Applicants. no date (Box 228, Folder 5)
      - Forms used by LWD. no date (Box 228, Folder 6)
      - U.S. Military Academy (publications). no date (Box 228, Folder 7)
      - U.S. Naval Academy (publications). no date (Box 228, Folder 8)
      - Air Corps (applicants). no date (Box 228, Folder 9)
      - Applicants, A-H. no date (Box 229)
      - Applicants, I-Z. no date (Box 230)
    - Political Campaign, 1932
      - Democratic National Committee. no date (Box 231, Folder 1)
      - Democratic Party Platform. no date (Box 231, Folder 2)
      - Democratic Party Convention, Chicago. June 1932 (Box 231, Folder 3)
      - Nomination Papers and Announcement. no date (Box 231, Folder 4)
      - LWD's Campaign Material. no date (Box 231, Folder 5)
      - Radio Speeches during campaign. no date (Box 231, Folder 6)
      - Financial Papers. no date (Box 231, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous campaign material. no date (Box 231, Folder 8)
      - Clippings. April 1931-December 1932 (Box 231, Folder 9-11)
      - Correspondence, general. June 1931-August 1932 (Box 232, Folder 1-5)
      - Correspondence, various. no date (Box 232, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, invitations to speak, attend meetings, etc. no date (Box 232, Folder 7)
      - Notebook (names and addresses of persons whom LWD assisted as a Congressman). no date (Box 232)
      - Republican Campaign Textbook. 1932 (Box 232)
      - Correspondence, general. September 1932 (Box 233, Folder 1-2)
      - Correspondence, primary election: congratulations. no date (Box 233, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, general. October 1932-April 1933 (Box 233, Folder 4-7)
      - Correspondence, general election: congratulations. no date (Box 233, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, regarding Ray Gilbert. no date (Box 233, Folder 9)
  - Subseries III: Director of the Budget, 1933-1934
    - Appointment (miscellaneous). no date (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Appointment (clippings). no date (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - Congratulations (acknowledged in person and unacknowledged). no date (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Congratulations (acknowledged by Mrs. Douglas). no date (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - Congratulations (general, A-L). no date (Box 234, Folder 5-12)
    - Congratulations (general, M-Z). no date (Box 235, Folder 1-6)
    - Budget suggestions (and additional congratulations). January 1933-February 1934 (Box 235, Folder 7-8)
    - Offers of assistance. no date (Box 235, Folder 9)
    - Personal memoranda, etc. (FDR, Budget, Cabinet). no date (Box 236, Folder 1-4)
    - Drafts of 1935 budget message. no date (Box 236, Folder 5-6)
    - Drafts of miscellaneous speeches for FDR. no date (Box 236, Folder 7)
    - Resignation correspondence, A-Z. no date (Box 236, Folder 8-10)
    - Business propositions on resigning as director. no date (Box 236, Folder 11)
    - Speech, Radio "Economy and Human Values." March 18, 1933 (Box 237, Folder 1)
    - Speech, Radio, Choosing-a-Career Conference. June 27, 1934 (Box 237, Folder 2)
    - Speech, Boston, 9th New England Conference. November 23, 1933 (Box 237, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous speeches. no date (Box 237, Folder 4)
    - Budget (general correspondence). no date (Box 237, Folder 5)
    - Budget (LWD's notes, memoranda, etc). no date (Box 237, Folder 6)
    - Budget (bills and legislation). no date (Box 237, Folder 7)
    - Budget (miscellaneous material). no date (Box 237, Folder 8)
    - Reorganization (general). no date (Box 237, Folder 9)
    - Reorganization (work with Sherley). no date (Box 237, Folder 10-11)
    - Correspondence (Robert Stroud and office). no date (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (Art Curlee). no date (Box 238, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (James A. Farley). no date (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (John Nance Garner, vice-president). no date (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (Col. Edward M. House). no date (Box 238, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (Walter Lippmann). no date (Box 238, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (Sir F.W. Leith Ross). no date (Box 238, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (Veterans, claims). no date (Box 238, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (Veterans, miscellaneous). no date (Box 238, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence ("Howls from the Lunatic Fringe"). no date (Box 238, Folder 10-11)
    - Magazine articles about LWD. no date (Box 238, Folder 12)
    - Clippings. February 1933-December 1934 (Box 238, Folder 13-14)
    - Correspondence (general, miscellaneous). no date (Box 239, Folder 1-4)
    - Correspondence (politics, Isabella Greenway). no date (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (politics, Arizona). no date (Box 239, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (politics, Walter Martin). no date (Box 239, Folder 7-10)
    - Correspondence (legislation, various). no date (Box 240, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (legislation, Veterans). no date (Box 240, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (irrigation districts, various). no date (Box 240, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (irrigation districts, Paradise-Verde). no date (Box 240, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (grazing, agriculture, cattle). no date (Box 240, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (federal buildings). no date (Box 240, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (loans; RFC). no date (Box 240, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (mining). no date (Box 240, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (various topics). no date (Box 240, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous Arizona problems). no date (Box 240, Folder 10)
    - Job requests (government, miscellaneous A-Z). no date (Box 241, Folder 1-6)
    - Job requests (government, Bureau of the Budget). no date (Box 241, Folder 7)
    - Job requests (government, PWA, CCC, construction work). no date (Box 241, Folder 8)
    - Job requests (government, Post Office, mail routes). no date (Box 241, Folder 9)
    - Requests (government, RFC, NRA, Home Owners Loan). no date (Box 242, Folder 1)
    - Requests (government, various). no date (Box 242, Folder 2)
    - Requests (miscellaneous). no date (Box 242, Folder 3)
    - Requests (Ray Gilbert, State Re-employment Director). no date (Box 242, Folder 4)
    - Requests (for appointments to Service Academies). no date (Box 242, Folder 5)
    - Requests (for articles and statements). no date (Box 242, Folder 6)
    - Requests (for autographs and photographs). no date (Box 242, Folder 7)
    - Requests (for information). no date (Box 242, Folder 8)
    - Requests (for interviews). no date (Box 242, Folder 9)
    - Requests (for publications). no date (Box 242, Folder 10)
    - Requests (for money). no date (Box 242, Folder 11)
    - Requests (acknowledgments for publications and gifts). no date (Box 242, Folder 12)
    - Requests (invitations). no date (Box 242, Folder 13)
    - Requests (letters of introduction and recommendation). no date (Box 242, Folder 14)
    - Requests (offers to sell). no date (Box 242, Folder 15)
    - Agriculture. no date (Box 243, Folder 1-2)
    - Unemployment and relief. no date (Box 243, Folder 3)
    - Veterans Administration (correspondence). no date (Box 243, Folder 4)
    - Veterans Administration (miscellaneous material). no date (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - Veterans Administration (special review board). no date (Box 243, Folder 6)
    - Veterans Administration (bills, notes, drafts of speeches for FDR). no date (Box 243, Folder 7)
    - Public Works (extracts from minutes of special board for public works). 1933 (Box 243, Folder 8)
    - Public Works (correspondence, notes, miscellaneous material). no date (Box 243, Folder 9)
    - Public Works (projects). no date (Box 243, Folder 10)
    - Special Board for Public Works, minutes. June-September 1933 (Box 244)
    - Speical Board for Public Works, minutes. October-December 5, 1933 (Box 245)
    - Special Board for Public Works, minutes. December 7-28, 1933 (Box 246)
    - Banking (correspondence, notes, memoranda). no date (Box 247, Folder 1)
    - Banking (miscellaneous reports, printed material). no date (Box 247, Folder 2)
    - Bank for Liquidation. no date (Box 247, Folder 3)
    - Gold. no date (Box 247, Folder 4)
    - Securities Act (correspondence). no date (Box 247, Folder 5-6)
    - Securities Act (bills, amendments, etc.). no date (Box 247, Folder 7)
    - Securities Act (miscellaneous material). no date (Box 247, Folder 8)
    - Colorado River. no date (Box 248, Folder 1)
    - Money (general correspondence). no date (Box 248, Folder 2)
    - Money (Greenback legislation). no date (Box 248, Folder 3)
    - Money ("Monetary Group" papers). no date (Box 248, Folder 4)
    - Money (miscellaneous material). no date (Box 248, Folder 5)
    - Foreign debts. no date (Box 248, Folder 6)
    - Taxes (correspondence). no date (Box 248, Folder 7)
    - Taxes (notes, memoranda, miscellaneous material). no date (Box 248, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous publications. no date (Box 248, Folder 9)
    - National Industry Recovery (hearings in Congress). no date (Box 249, Folder 1)
    - National Industry Recovery (correspondence, bills, NRA, etc.). no date (Box 249, Folder 2)
    - Capital Goods and Heavy Industries (miscellaneous material). no date (Box 249, Folder 3)
    - Capital Goods and Heavy Industries (correspondence). no date (Box 249, Folder 4)
    - Home Owners' Loan Corporation. no date (Box 249, Folder 5)
    - Construction League. no date (Box 249, Folder 6)
    - Recovery Plans (general). no date (Box 249, Folder 7)
    - American Cyanamid (appointment, clippings, miscellaneous correspondence). no date (Box 250, Folder 1)
    - American Cyanamid (European trip, correspondence and report to W.B. Bell). 1934-1935 (Box 250, Folder 2)
    - American Cyanamid (European trip, miscellaneous material). 1934-1935 (Box 250, Folder 3)
    - American Cyanamid (European trip, notes, diary, report). 1937 (Box 250, Folder 4)
    - American Cyanamid (European trip, miscellaneous material). 1937 (Box 250, Folder 5)
    - American Cyanamid (Company policy and inflation, recommendations by LWD and others). no date (Box 250, Folder 6)
    - American Cyanamid (correspondence with W.B. Bell and others. ). 1939-1943 (Box 250, Folder 7)
    - American Cyanamid ("Drafts of proposed political platforms"). no date (Box 250, Folder 8)
    - American Cyanamid ("Corporate Tax Work"). 1934-1935 (Box 250, Folder 9)
    - American Cyanamid (miscellaneous notes). no date (Box 250, Folder 10)
    - National Life Insurance Company. 1938-1940 (Box 250, Folder 11)
    - Brochure on France, put out by French Line--souvenir of one of LWD's trips at this time. no date (Box 250)
  - Subseries IV: Politics and World Affairs, 1935-1947